{
    "subject": "Yves_Angelo",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Colonel_Chabert__1994_film_",
    "human_readable": "Yves Angelo created the film Colonel Chabert (1994).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9693095088005066,
            "question": "What film was created in 1994 by Yves Angelo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8526058197021484,
            "question": "Which filmmaker created Colonel Chabert?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8472517132759094,
            "question": "Is Colonel Chabert a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8431757688522339,
            "question": "In what year was the film Colonel Chabert made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8109472393989563,
            "question": "Who directed the film Colonel Chabert?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7537161111831665,
            "question": "What year was the film Colonel Chabert released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6990233659744263,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Yves Angelo."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6984910368919373,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Yves Angelo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6675389409065247,
            "question": "What type of work did Yves Angelo create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6569141149520874,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Yves Angelo?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Yves Angelo created the film Colonel Chabert (1994).",
            "html": "yago_14898_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work did Yves Angelo create?",
            "html": "yago_14898_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the film directed by Yves Angelo?",
            "html": "yago_14898_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film directed by Yves Angelo.",
            "html": "yago_14898_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14898_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14898_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14898_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14898_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14898_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14898_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14898_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14898_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14898_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14898_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the required format:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Yves Angelo directing and creating the film \"Le Colonel Chabert\" in 1994, which supports the statement that Yves Angelo created the film \"Colonel Chabert (1994).\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}